{
    "subject": "resource/Erich_Regener",
    "predicate": "ontology/citizenship",
    "object": "resource/Germany",
    "human_readable": "Erich Regener is a citizen of Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9714415073394775,
            "question": "Does Erich Regener hold German citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392446279525757,
            "question": "Is Erich Regener German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8548439741134644,
            "question": "Is Germany Erich Regener's home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8196718096733093,
            "question": "What is Erich Regener's citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.804958164691925,
            "question": "Erich Regener is a citizen of...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7252089977264404,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Erich Regener?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6759722232818604,
            "question": "What is Erich Regener's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6558399796485901,
            "question": "To which country does Erich Regener belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312754154205322,
            "question": "In which country was Erich Regener born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6254972815513611,
            "question": "Where is Erich Regener from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Erich Regener is a citizen of Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7929_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country was Erich Regener born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7929_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Erich Regener belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7929_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Erich Regener's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7929_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7929_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Erich Regener was a German physicist.  This implies he was a citizen of Germany."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Erich Regener was a German physicist, which implies that he was a citizen of Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Erich Regener was a German physicist, including details about his work in Germany and his nationality."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}